Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Audio Visual
  - Subseries 6: No Regret
    - No Regret - Reggie Williams, 1991; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - No Regret - Reggie Williams, 1991; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - No Regret - Williams/Lee, 1991; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Disclosure - Photos of Reggie Williams and Michael Lee
    - No Regret - Recording Studio, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Recorded on 18 Apr 1992
    - No Regret - Recording Studio, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - No Regret - Slo Mo, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 20mins (Box 27, Folder 17)
      Disclosure - 3rd cut
    - No Regret - Stills, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 19)
      Stills of Michael, Joe, Magic
    - No Regret - Audio Transfer, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 20)
      Audio transfer recorded 06 May 1992
    - No Regret - Civil Rights Music, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 27, Folder 99)
      Music #99
    - Floppy Discs, 1992; 5.25 inch (Box 93)
      3 floppy discs with 'Fear of Disclosure' information, 1992
    - No regret - Tillery/Blackberri, 1992; Audio: 1/4 inch reel (Box 153, Folder 13)
      Mixed on 29 Apr 1992 - contains audio of performance by Linda Tillery, Blackberri and the voice of Marlon Riggs
    - No Regret - Protection Copy, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 902)
      No Regret - Protection Copy - 15 May 1992
    - No Regret - Protection Copy, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 903)
      No Regret - Protection Copy - 20 May 1992
    - No Regret - Fear of Disclosure, Video: Betacam SP; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 904)
      SubMaster - 13 May 1992
    - No Regret, Video: Betacam SP (Box 186, Folder 905)
      Sealed Copy
    - Fear of Disclosure: No Regret, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; (Box 186, Folder 906)
      Edited Master - 15 May 1992
    - No Regret - Final cut copy, Video: Umatic; 40mins (Box 186, Folder 907)
      Final version copy
    - No Regret - Rough Cut, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 909)
      Rough cut 7a
    - No Regret - Rough Cut, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 910)
      Rough cut 7b
    - No Regret - Rough Cut, Video: Umatic (Box 186, Folder 911)
      Rough 2
    - No Regret - Rough Cut, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 912)
      Rough 4
    - No Regret - Rough Cut, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 913)
      Rough 5
    - No Regret - Rough Cut, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 186, Folder 914)
      Rough 6
    - No Regret - Window Dub, 1992; Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 187, Folder 11)
      audio: discrete - from 08 Feb 1992
    - No Regret - Title and Song, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 187, Folder 18)
      We're not supposed to talk about it' and Steve Langley 'I tried'
    - No Regret - Steve Langley, 1992; Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 187, Folder 20)
    - No Regret - Fine Cut, Video: Umatic (Box 187, Folder 517)
      Rough Cut 7a - sound A Roll 5/6
    - Fear of Disclosure: No Regret, Video: 1inch reel (Box 233, Folder 908)
      37:44 Dir: Jonathan Lee
    - No Regret, 1992; Video: 2inch reel; 37mins (Box 248)
      from 18 May 1992
  - Subseries 7: Anthem
    - Anthem -Master Audio, Video: Betacam SP; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 1)
      Ch. 1 & 2
    - Anthem -Master Audio, Video: Betacam SP; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Ch. 3 & 4 (first 10mins), also Ch. 5 & 6
    - Anthem -Master Audio & Video B Roll, Video: Betacam SP; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Audio Music Ch. 7 & 8
    - Anthem -Master Audio & Video C Roll, Video: Betacam SP; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 4)
      Audio Music Ch. 9 & 10
    - Anthem -Dub, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 5)
      Dub of latest Rough - with Title
    - Anthem: Edited Master, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Anthem -Flags, Video: Betacam SP;; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 7)
      America by Blackberri (with choir)
    - Anthem: Outdoor Flags, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 8)
      PUR Stock Footage
    - Anthem -Colin's Lips #2, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Anthem -Costume Dance, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 10)
      Marlon dancing - also BIBA Tape No. 285
    - Anthem -African Dance Footage, Video: Betacam SP;; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 11)
      African Dance and America by Blackberri (without choir)
    - Anthem Various shots, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 12)
      Footage of Fists, Rose, Cross, Vaseline, Candles and Candlelight vigil
    - Anthem -Graphics, Video: Betacam;; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 13)
      Graphics (text) from Macintosh
    - Anthem: Pink Triangles, Video: Betacam;; 5mins (Box 61, Folder 14)
      Original Images
    - Anthem -Smiling Lips, Video: Betacam;; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 15)
      Mock Video, Nicole Kiss, last 10min Marlon studio costume
    - Paintbox Graphics for Anthem, 1991; Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 16)
      Graphics by Chris Robbins (18 Jan 1991) Tape 1
    - Paintbox Graphics for Anthem, 1991; Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 17)
      Graphics by Chris Robbins (18 Jan 1991) Tape 2
    - Anthem, Video: Umatic;; 30mins (Box 61, Folder 18)
      Screening copy
    - Anthem: Rough Cut, Video: Umatic;; 20mins (Box 61, Folder 19)
      Early Draft rough cut
    - Anthem - Music Master, Video: Betacam SP;; 60mins (Box 61, Folder 20)
      Push/Pull - whole CD and America the Beautiful
  - Subseries 8: Black Is...Black Ain't
    - BIBA #605, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 40)
      Riggs interviewed about church going practices
    - BIBA, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 24, Folder 42)
      Portrait of Jason
    - Unity Church Interviews, 1992; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 1)
      Unity Church Interviews from 22 May 1992
    - Lyle Harris, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 2)
      Interview with Lyle Harris Pt1 & 2
    - Lyle Harris, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 3)
      Interview with Lyle Harris Pt3 & 4
    - Lyle Harris, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 4)
      Interview with Lyle Harris Pt5 & 6
    - First and Last Words (Radio Series of poetry and spoken word), Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 5)
      Side I - Aaren Perry and Ramona Hymen, Side II - Linh Dinh and Nzadi Zimele Keita
    - First and Last Words (Radio Series of poetry and spoken word), Audio:: Cassette Tape; 60mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 6)
      Side III - Essex Hemphill with Larry Duckette, Side IV - Eugene Howard and Carol Ann Robertson
    - Bellas music/Duckette/Essex, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 7)
      Larry Duckette, Essex and Gary, Steve Langley (marlon asks for peoples wishes)
    - Waysons sample tape, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 8)
      MUSIC - Urban Odyssey theme
    - Work tape for BIBA, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 25, Folder 25)
      Mary Watkins
    - BIBA demo's, Film: 16mm col/mute pos (Box 30, Folder 1)
      2 short reels of demo's for BIBA from Film Craft and FourMedia
    - BIBA - L.A. shots, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 1)
      Ext days shots of LA - Recorded 19 May 1992
    - BIBA -Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 2)
      Performance at Highways, LA, on 19 May 1992
    - BIBA -Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - BIBA -Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - BIBA -South central LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 5)
      Unknown content (logs mention interviews with south central LA Youths)
    - BIBA -South central LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - BIBA -South central LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 7)
      Unknown content (logs mention EH/MR lecture)
    - BIBA -Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 8)
      Performance at Moviehouse on 20 May 1992
    - BIBA -Unity Rally, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 9)
      interviews with various people at the LA Unity Rally
    - BIBA -Gongs LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 10)
      Ext shots outside Moviehouse and interview with Valerie Wagner - filmed on 21 and 22 May 1992
    - BIBA -Interviews LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 11)
      Interviews with Valerie Wagner, James D Miller and Charisse Brown on 22 May 1992
    - BIBA -Interviews LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 12)
      Interviews with Charisse Brown and Bishop Carl Bean filmed at the Unity Church in LA on 22 May 1992
    - BIBA -Interviews LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 13)
      Interviews with Bishop Carl Bean and Leslie Burke filmed at the Unity Church in LA on 22 May 1992
    - BIBA -Interviews LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 14)
      Interviews with Leslie Burke, Ronald William Smith and Roger Quinney filmed at the Unity Church in LA on 22 May 1992
    - BIBA -Interviews LA, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 15)
      Interviews with Roger Quinney and Vera F Owens filmed at the Unity Church in LA on 22 May 1992. Group at the Dandelion Café
    - BIBA - Group, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 16)
      Group at the Dandelion Café on 23 May 1992
    - BIBA - Group, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - BIBA - Group, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 18)
      Group at the Dandelion Café on 23 May 1992 and Barbours Shop
    - BIBA - Barbours Shop, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 19)
      Barber Shop
    - BIBA - Lyle's House party, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 20)
      Lyle's House Party
    - BIBA - Party, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 21)
      Party at the Unity Church LA on 23 May 1992
    - BIBA - Unity Church, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 22)
      Filmed at the Unity Church LA on 24 May 1992
    - BIBA - Unity Church, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 23)
      Filmed at the Unity Church LA
    - BIBA - Lyle Harris, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 24)
      Interview with Lyle Harris in LA on 25 May 1992
    - BIBA - Lyle Harris, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - BIBA - Lyle Harris, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - BIBA - Lyle Harris, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 27)
      Interview and photos with Lyle Harris in LA on 25 May 1992
    - BIBA - Photos, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 28)
      Photos taken in LA on 25 May 1992
    - BIBA - Film transfer, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 29)
      Black Is Black Ain't - Film to tape transfer CR 1-2, 4, 5
    - BIBA - Film transfer, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 68, Folder 30)
      Black Is Black Ain't - Film to tape transfer CR 3-4
    - BIBA - Shelton School, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 31)
      social graces/meditation
    - BIBA - Shelton School, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 32)
      Reading Lang.
    - BIBA - Shelton School, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 33)
      interviews at Shelton Academy
    - BIBA - Shelton School, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 34)
      filmed 05 Jun 1992 - Shelton Academy and shots of playground
    - BIBA - Shelton School, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 35)
      Shelton Academy - singing and photo collages
    - BIBA - Shelton School, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 36)
      Stills - filmed 05 Jun 1992 - also readings and drawings 'An Enchanted Hair tale'
    - BIBA - Step Show, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 37)
      Step Show and fraternity interviews
    - BIBA - Step Show, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 38)
      Delta interview and Step Show
    - BIBA - Step Show, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 39)
      Step Show
    - BIBA - Step Show, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 40)
      Step Show and interview with Michael Franti
    - BIBA - Michael Franti, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 41)
      interview with Michael Franti
    - BIBA - Michael Franti, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - BIBA - Yoruba village, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 43)
      Yoruba African village of Oyotunji in South Carolina - filmed on 04 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Yoruba village, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - BIBA - Yoruba village, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 45)
      Unknown content (logs mention interview with chief and 2 young girls)
    - BIBA - Yoruba village, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 46)
      King and Queen (African village?)
    - BIBA - Yoruba village, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 47)
      King and Queen (African village?) filmed 05 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Yoruba village, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - BIBA - Sea Island, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 49)
      Interviews with Elting Smalls, Reddick, Wine - filmed on 06 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Sea Island, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - BIBA - Sea Island, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 51)
    - BIBA - Sea Island, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 52)
    - BIBA - Sea Island, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 53)
      Johnson and Robinson families - filmed on 06 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Sea Island, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 54)
    - BIBA - Transfer, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 55)
      Signifyin' Works - CR 7,8 (logs mention African village and Rural shots of South carolina)
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 56)
      Drew, Mississippi - Interview with Mrs Frances Morris on 09 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 57)
      Drew, Mississippi - Interview with Mrs Frances Morris and teenage children on 09 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 58)
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 59)
      Drew, Mississippi - Interview with teenage children on 09 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 69, Folder 60)
      Drew, Mississippi - Interview with teenage children and Dublin, Mississippi- Mrs Martin fishing on 09 Jul 1992 and 10 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 61)
      Mrs Martin fishing and exts of Dublin, Mississippi - filmed on 10 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Catfish Farm, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 62)
      Interview with Mr Scott at Catfish farm in Drew, Mississippi on 10 and 11 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Mississippi Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 63)
      Interview with Mr and Mrs Scott in Drew, Mississippi on 11 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Mississippi Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 64)
    - BIBA - Mississippi Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 65)
      Interview with Mr and Mrs Milton and Eva McWilliams in Drew Mississippi - also interview with T.J.Powell in Charleston, Mississippi on 11 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Mississippi Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 66)
      Interview with T.J.Powelland Mrs Powell in Charleston, Mississippi on 11 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Mississippi Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 67)
      Interview with Elder Freddy Drummer of St Johns Church, Drew, Mississippi on 12 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Mississippi Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 68)
    - BIBA - Transfer, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 69)
      Signifyin' Works - Tail 9, 10, 11 (logs mention interview with Mr Ben Johnson)
    - BIBA - Transfer, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 70)
      Signifyin' Works - CR 12, 13 (logs mention 'The Delta Blues Band'
    - BIBA - Transfer, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 70)
      Signifyin' Works - CR 14, 15 (logs mention Church shots and blues band)
    - BIBA - Angela Davis, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 71)
      Interviewed on 17 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Angela Davis, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 72)
    - BIBA - Angela Davis, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 73)
    - BIBA - Angela Davis, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 74)
    - BIBA - Angela Davis and Bloods, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 75)
      Angela Davis interviewed on 17 Jul 1992 in San Francisco and Bloods interviewed at South Central LA car wash on 20 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Bloods, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 76)
      Bloods interviewed at South Central LA car wash on 20 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Bloods, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 77)
    - BIBA - LA Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 78)
      Bloods interviewed at South Central LA car wash on 20 Jul 1992, also shots of Palm Trees in LA, and interview with Dr Mauluna Karenga in LA on 21 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Dr Karenga, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 79)
      Interview with Dr Mauluna Karenga in LA on 21 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Dr Karenga, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 80)
    - BIBA - Dr Karenga, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 81)
    - BIBA -Mr Ulysses Ricard, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 82)
      Interview with Mr Ulysses S. Ricard in New Orleans on 23 Jul 1992
    - BIBA -Mr Ulysses Ricard, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 83)
      Interview and stills with MrUlysses S. Ricard in New Orleans on 23 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Stills, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 84)
      stills of New Orleans on 23 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 85)
      Interview with Michael Decuir at the Southern University of New Orleans on 23 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - French Market, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 74, Folder 86)
      French Market shots and Kenneth Ferdinand
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 87)
      Interview with Kenneth Ferdinand on 24 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 88)
      Interview with Kenneth Ferdinand and Mrs Borders on 24 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 89)
      Interview with Mrs Borders on 24 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 90)
      Interview with Aline St. Julien on 25 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 91)
      Interview with Mrs Borders on 24 Jul 1992 and Ms Aline St. Julien
    - BIBA - New Orleans Interviews, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 92)
      Stills of Aline St. Julien and family dancing - filmed on 25 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Bell Hooks, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 93)
      Interview with Bell Blair Hooks in NYC on 28 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Bell Hooks, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 94)
    - BIBA - Bell Hooks, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 95)
    - BIBA - Cornel West, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 96)
      Interview with Cornel West on 28 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Cornel West, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 97)
    - BIBA - Cornel West, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 98)
    - BIBA - Molefi Asante, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 99)
      Interview with Dr Molefi Asante in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania on 25 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Molefi Asante, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 100)
    - BIBA - Molefi Asante, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 101)
    - BIBA - Asante and Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 102)
      Interview with Dr Molefi Asante in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania on 29 Jul 1992 and Essex Hemphill on 30 Jul 1992 in Philadelphia
    - BIBA - Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 103)
      Interview with Essex Hemphill on 30 Jul 1992 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
    - BIBA - Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 104)
    - BIBA - Essex Hemphill, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 105)
    - BIBA - Hemphill/Cabrera, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 106)
      Interview with Essex Hemphill on 30 Jul 1992 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and interview with Radamase Cabrera in Clinton, Prince George's County, Maryland on 31 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Radamase Cabrera, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 107)
      Interview with Radamase Cabrera in Clinton, Prince George's County, Maryland on 31 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - Radamase Cabrera, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 108)
      Interview and stills with Radamase Cabrera in Clinton, Prince George's County, Maryland on 31 Jul 1992 - also Barrow and Edith Harvey
    - BIBA - The Harveys, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 110)
      Interview with Barron and Edith Harvey in Prince George's County, Maryland on 31 Jul 1992
    - BIBA - The Harveys, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 111)
    - BIBA - The Harveys, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 112)
    - BIBA - CBM Inc, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 113)
      Concerned Black Men Inc - filmed at Nixon's Farm, Maryland on 01 Aug 1992
    - BIBA - The Riggs, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 114)
      Film of Riggs' family filmed on 02 Aug 1992
    - BIBA - The Riggs, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 115)
    - BIBA - The Riggs, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 116)
    - BIBA - The Riggs, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 117)
    - BIBA - The Riggs, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 118)
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 81, Folder 119)
      Interview with Bill T. Jones, filmed at NYC on 08 Aug 1992
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 120)
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 121)
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 122)
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 123)
      Performance of Bill T. Jones dancing, filmed on 09 Aug 1992
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 124)
    - BIBA - Bill T. Jones, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 125)
    - BIBA - African Burial Ground, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 126)
      Ext shots of the African Burial ground in NYC and interview with a brother on 11 Aug 1992
    - BIBA - Michele Wallace, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 127)
      Interview with Michele Wallace in Brooklyn, NYC on 11 Aug 1992
    - BIBA - Michele Wallace, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 128)
    - BIBA - Michele Wallace, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 129)
    - BIBA - London, England, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 130)
      Interviews with Paul Gilroy, Ingrid Pollard and Isaac Julien (from 28 Aug 1992)
    - BIBA - London, England, 1992; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 82, Folder 131)